JOSEPH PEREZ

Toronto, ON (647) 512-3299 josephpd95@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated and hard-working individual with more than 5 years of experience in the construction industry including demolition, residential construction, and carpentry

Displays exceptional problem-solving skills and works efficiently to meet project deadlines while ensuring client satisfaction

SKILLS

Interpersonal	Organizational	Adaptability	Problem Solving
Communication	Time Management	Arithmetic	Bilingual (Spanish)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RECO, Toronto, On

Handyman, October 2020 – Present

- Responsible for finishing new condo units and eliminating any trade related deficiencies
- In charge of completing any new condo unit repairs such as: Laundry machine hook ups, drywall repair, faucet installation, painting, home installations, flooring repair, baseboard repair, Door staining repair, etc.
- Punctual arriving to three new condo development sites

THE SHED INSTALLER GUYS, TORONTO, ON

Carpenter and installer, Mar 2015 – Sep 2019

- Lead home improvement projects assembling prefabricated and custom-built sheds
- Worked in a team of 4-5 people while ensure project deadlines were safely met
- Assisted Lead Carpenter with excavation, construction, and disposal of materials
- Safely operated various power tools such as reciprocating saws, electric and hand drills

E.C.U PAINTING, TORONTO, ON

Handyman, May 2011 - Sep 2016

- Assisted carpenters and painters with framing, mudding, tiling, and painting for home renovation projects
- Collaborated with external companies to ensure project requirements were fulfilled according to the client's request
- Cleaned and maintained work areas and equipment to ensure a safe and efficient work environment

EDUCATION

GEORGE BROWN COLLEGE, TORONTO ON

Renovation Technology Program, 2018

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Ability to physically lift and carry up to 80 lbs.
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills in both written and spoken English and Spanish
- Ability to read and interpret blueprints
- Expert operation of power and hand tools
- Excellent team player and demonstrates leadership skills to ensure tasks are completed accurately and efficiently